[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "Portugal",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Amsterdam"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Lisbon"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Madrid"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Monaco"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "South Korea",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Seoul"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Singapore"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Beijing"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Manila"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Madagascar",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Brazzaville"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Dakar"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Georgetown"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Antananarivo"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "New Zealand",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Canberra"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Wellington"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Suva"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Port Moresby"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Peru",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Santiago"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Asunción"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Lima"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Caracas"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "Armenia",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Yerevan"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Bern"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Tbilisi"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Tallinn"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Thailand",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Hanoi"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Bangkok"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Kuala Lumpur"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Vientiane"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Canada",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Mexico City"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Nuuk"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Havana"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Ottawa"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 4
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "Egypt",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Tripoli"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Cairo"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Rabat"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Ottawa"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "Uruguay",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "content": "Buenos Aires"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "content": "Bogotá"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "content": "Quito"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "content": "Montevideo"
      }
    ],
    "correctOption": 4
  }
]
